



Guricheva Vera

Female, 23 years, born on 22 January 1999

+7 (952) 3866435 vera22227@yandex.ru — preferred means of communication

Reside in: Atyrau Citizenship: Russia

Ready to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

650 **QA Engineer** USD

Specializations:

Tester

Employment: full time

Work schedule: remote working, full day

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 10 months

June 2022 — November 2022 6 months

Yandex Practicum

QA Engineer

- Analysis of the requirements for the Yandex Scooter service, including using mind-map and flowcharts;
- Application of test design techniques for Yandex Forms: equivalence classes, boundary values, pairwise;
- Compilation of checklists, test cases and bug reports in Yandex Tracker and TestRail;
- Working with DevTools to search for bugs in Yandex Taxi;
- Testing the Yandex Counter API with Charles and Postman;
- Writing queries to the application database using PostgreSQL.

February 2020 — March 2020 2 months

Petropolitana tour

Office manager

- Preparation of tourist documentation;
- Posting tours on the company's website;
- Work with incoming calls.

June 2019 — July 2019 2 months

Envy Box

Call center operator

- Consultations on electronic widgets of the online store (online chat, callback, pop-ups, etc.);
- Work in the CRM system;
- Analysis of the statistics of the client's website.

Education

Vocational secondary

2019 **Russian College of Traditional Culture**

Tourism, Tourism

Key skills

Languages Russian — Native

English — B2 — Upper Intermediate

Skills

Test analysis Test design Functional testing Regression testing SQL PostgreSQL Java JavaScript SOAP REST JSON API XML **Charles Proxy** Postman Atlassian Jira TestRail Swagger

Further information

About me

I want to help develop a product that society needs in a large team. In my life I try to improve the quality of everything around me, not just software:) This is how I satisfy my inner perfectionist. In the future, I see myself as a QA automatisation engineer- I know the Java programming language well.

I know the HTTP(S) and SHH protocols and know how to use the browser console. Worked with Jira and Confluence. I can test the API in Postman and the mobile app in Android Studio, remove logs in ADB.

Now I live in Kazakhstan, but I am considering remote work options both here and in Russia and other countries!